饥饿
的青春
第二季  第二十集
0,0,0,fx,学习
0,0,0,fx,分享
0,0,0,fx,进步
本字幕由ZiMuZu原创翻译
最新下载请登录www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻译   阿包说爱我
翻译  roaddog
校对  阿包憋说话吻我
时间轴  阿包说爱我
后期 斯人       总监 阿包憋说话吻我
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    ustvboom
了解最新影视字幕发布信息
《饥饿的青春》前情回顾
Previously on Young & Hungry.
这是我弟弟杰克
This is my younger brother, Jack.
我想做大厨
I want to be a chef.
好了  差不多了  我来教你
Okay, you're almost there, let me show you...
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
我一定要赶他走的真正原因是...
The real reason I wanted my brother to go away...
我对你还...
is because I have...
天呐
Oh, my god!
加比和杰克的餐车
我为我和加比弄了一辆餐车
I got this food truck for me and Gabi!
-什么鬼...  -我爱死啦
- What a piece of... - I love it!
怎么样
So...
餐车如何
how about that truck?
是不是像你一样漂亮
Isn't she a beauty? Just like you.
车上写着我的名字
It has my name on it.
弟弟  弟弟...
Bro, bro, bro...
我有点糊涂了
I'm a little confused.
你应该在去那所我替你付了一大笔学费的
You were on your way to a very expensive cooking school
烹饪学校报到的路上
that I wrote a very big check for.
而你现在开着辆餐车...
And now you stand before me...
出现在我面前
with a food truck.
车上还有我的名字
That has my name on it.
我理解你  伙计
I totally get your confusion, man.
我坐在出租上赶往机场
And I was in a cab going to the airport.
脑子里全是加比  突然间
And I was thinking about Gabi when all of a sudden,
我看见这辆餐车在出售
I see this food truck for sale.
我说  "停车"
I was like, "Stop."
对司机说  "司机  靠边停车"
I told the cabbie, "You pull over, cabbie!"
然后我就把它买下来了
And then I bought it.
用我给你的三万六千元吗
With the $36,000 I gave you?
别高兴太早
That's not how you shwah.
你别高兴太早
That is not how you shwah!
加比是名优秀的大厨
Look, Gabi's an amazing cook,
为什么我不能边学厨艺边赚钱呢
so why shouldn't I learn and make money at the same time?
得了吧  杰克
Oh come on, Jake!
你两周换一份工作
You change jobs every two weeks.
凭什么觉得加比会和你一起
What makes you think Gabi's just gonna jump on the crazy train
经营这辆餐车
and start a food truck with you?
她才说了她喜欢
She just said she loved it.
那是她出于礼貌
Well, she was being polite.
告诉他你的心里话  加比
Tell him how you feel, Gabi.
这是别人为我做过最浪漫的事了
This is the nicest thing that anybody's ever done for me.
而且车上还有我名字
And it has my name on it.
您好[意第绪语]
Shalom.
我和埃兰今天要和夏皮罗拉比会面
Alan and I are meeting with Rabbi Shapiro today.
"关我屁事"该怎么用意第绪语来说
Um... what's Yiddish for "who cares?"
埃兰的妈妈说
According to Alan's mother,
我们得在他主持婚礼之前得到他的祝福
we need him to give us his blessing before he marries us.
由他主持婚礼的伴侣不会离婚
No couple he's married has ever divorced.
真是太糟了
Oh, that's too bad.
因为我特别招离婚男士的喜爱
'Caused divorced men are my specialty.
你还没找到参加婚礼的男伴吗
Oh, you still can't find a date to my wedding?
这在意第绪语里是"令人震惊"的意思
That's Yiddish for "what a shocker."
早上好
Good morning.
这是加比和杰克餐车的加比吗
Is that Gabi from Gabi and Jake's food truck?
是的
Yeah, it is.
我以为你忙着和我弟弟杰克驾车在城里乱转呢
I thought you'd be busy driving around town with Jake, my brother.
没  我在这给老板您做早餐呢
No, I'm here cooking breakfast for you, my boss,
因为这是我的工作
'cause that's my job.
你觉得你可以兼顾两边吗
You think you can do both jobs?
是的  我白天在这里为你工作
Yeah, I'm gonna work here for you during the day,
晚上经营餐车
and I'm gonna take the truck out at night.
你不介意的  对吧
That's cool with you, right?
是的  加比  我丝毫不介意
Yes, Gabi. That's totally cool.
那你笑什么
Why is that funny?
有什么可笑的
没什么
No reason.
我敢打包票
I am completely positive and confident
这会是一个明智的  有利可图的决定
this will be a wise and lucrative decision.
真的吗  因为我觉得
Really? Because, you know,
你说话的语气在暗示些什么
your tone is kind of suggesting otherwise.
可能是因为我想知道从昨晚起
Well, I suppose my tone might be pondering the notion
你对于此事考虑了哪些方面
of how much thought you put into this,
说话才会是这种语气
you know, since last night.
具体来说  你们的目标消费群是什么
More specifically what's your culinary target market,
有特定的专营市场吗
is there a certain niche being under-served,
你们的销售策略是什么
and what's your marketing strategy?
好像这些我们都没考虑过一样
Yeah, like we haven't thought through all that already.
好吧  是没考虑过
Okay, we haven't.
但你知道为什么吗
But you want to know why?
因为和你不同
Because unlike you,
我和杰克没脑子
me and Jake don't think...
我们有
We do.
-你说有就有吧  -真的  好吗
- If you say so. - I do, okay?
这事一定会大获成功的
This is gonna be a huge success.
想知道为什么吗
Do you want to know why?
因为餐车上写着我们的名字
Because we have a food truck with our name on it!
有什么东西上面写着你的名字吗
What do you have with your name on it?
公司的办公大楼  不计其数的杂志封面
A corporate office building, numerous magazine covers,
我每周开给你的支票
the check I write you every week.
加比和杰克
这餐车一定能赚很多钱
This truck is gonna make so much money!
然后我把钱都存进银行
And I'm gonna open a bank account,
乔什会大吃一惊
and Josh is gonna be like, "what?"
我不明白你为什么要这么做
Yeah, well I'm already like, "why?"
加比  你想过经营餐车的问题吗
Gabi, have you thought any of this through?
在乔什让我意识到我没想过之后
Well, after Josh made me think I didn't,
我想了一下
I did.
我想把给婚礼准备餐点赚的钱
I'm gonna use the money I make catering the wedding
用来购买原材料  制作放在餐车上卖的餐食
to buy the ingredients to make the food I sell in the food truck.
该死  乔什问我的时候我怎么没想到
Damn it! Why didn't I think of that when Josh asked me?
好吧  我只觉得这有点太天真
Okay. I just think it's a little bit naive.
实在不明白你为什么要为一个男人
I really don't understand why you'd risk everything
不惜一切...  你好
over a guy-- hi.
-我叫索菲亚  -我叫杰克
- I'm Sofia. - I'm Jake.
你有兄弟吗
Do you have any brothers?
-有  乔什  -我明白了
- Yes-- Josh. - Oh, right.
很高兴见到你
It's nice to meet you.
我要去检查一下进气管
I am going to check on the intake manifold.
-我故意这么说耍帅的  -你成功了
- I just said that to impress you. - It worked.
我想含住他的管子[丁丁]
I'd like to intake his manifold.
加比穿着短裙站在肮脏小巷里
Gabi in a short skirt in a dirty alleyway.
有些事突然解释通了
Some things just make sense.
小加加  你好
Gabala, hey.
我妈妈打电话来了
So, my mom called.
说好多客人都是只吃洁食的
It turns out a lot of our guests eat strictly kosher,
所以开胃菜也得是洁食
So the appetizers have to be, too.
好吧  那我就做成洁食
Oh, okay. Well, I'll just make them kosher.
我要怎么办
What do I gotta do to them?
在新厨房里全部重做一遍
Make them all again in a whole new kitchen.
洁食得用犹太教认可的设备做
Kosher food has to be prepared in a kosher facility.
或许这餐车里的厨房
Well, hey, maybe the kitchen
都是认可的设备
in this food truck is a kosher facility.
这餐车可是头猪  亲爱的
It's in the shape of a pig, sweetheart,
恐怕不会是
So, I'm guessing no.
抱歉  加比
I'm sorry, Gabi.
如果这能让你好受点  我一开始
If it helps... I never wanted you to be
就不想让你负责的
a part of this in the first place.
我的梦想破灭了
Well, there went my dreams.
天啊  加比
Oh, god, Gabi.
真对不起
I am so sorry.
杰克  我刚被婚礼开除了
Jake, I just got fired from the wedding,
现在我身无分文
And now all I have is no money
却有一千份非洁食小吃
and a thousand non-kosher appetizers.
这多棒
That's sweet!
你有小吃  我们有餐车
You have food-- we have a food truck!
今晚就带它出去遛遛吧
Let's take this baby for a spin tonight.
天啊  这主意好棒
Oh, my god. That's an amazing idea!
棒的是你
You're an amazing idea.
好吧
Oh, okay.
还记得你说我们
Remember how amazing you were
可以把小吃卖给一大堆人时
when you said we could sell my appetizers
我夸你好棒吗
to a whole bunch of people,
你却带我来个不见人影的公园
and then you took me to a park where there are no people?
某人是紧张了吗
Is somebody a little nervous?
加比  没事的
Gabi, it's all good.
我捕鲔船上认识的兄弟艾德
My buddy Ed from my tuna boat days
在附近有场小演出
is playing a small gig near here,
我保证大家看完了表演会饿的
and I'm sure people are gonna be hungry after his show.
小演出吗
A small gig?
我们可有一千份小吃要卖
We have a thousand appetizers to sell.
如果乔什是对的怎么办  我们的生意失败
I mean, what if Josh is right? What if our business fails
不再是生意伙伴了
and we're no longer business partners,
然后不再是任何伙伴
and then we're no longer any type of partners,
然后我们...我们...
and-- and then we... we're not a--
我真的很喜欢你
I am really into you.
是吗
You are?
还有...
And another thing...
天啊
Oh, my god.
你捕鲔船上认识的艾德是谁
Um... who is Ed from the tuna boat?
他姓希兰
Oh, his last name is Sheeran.
艾德·希兰吗
Ed Sheeran?
那个跟霉霉是闺蜜的格莱美提名歌手
The Grammy nominee who's best friends with Taylor Swift?
什么  我以为我才是他闺蜜呢
What? I thought I was his best friend.
乔尔  我是教堂唱诗班的尤兰达
Hi, Joel, this is Yolanda from church choir...
我周六有个小活动
I have this little event on Saturday,
在想你愿不愿...
and I was just wondering--
你老婆从昏迷中苏醒了吗
Oh, your wife came out of that coma?
恭喜你
Congrats.
永久性植物人个屁
Permanent vegetative state, my ass.
真是有爱
Isn't this cute?
加比和杰克给他们的餐车开了个推特账号
Gabi and Jake started a Twitter account for their food truck.
刚刚发了一张他俩和艾德·希兰的合影
They just tweeted a photo of Gabi, Jake, and Ed Sheeran.
"餐车超火爆  #上帝保佑
"We are killing it, hashtag blessed,
#快卖完了"
"Hashtag almost sold out."
你猜怎么着  尤兰达
Well, guess what, Yolanda?
"快卖完了"根本比不上...
"Almost sold out" Is a lot different than--
"#卖完了"
"Hashtag sold out."
谢谢
Thank you.
我们成功了
We did it!
警官  我们刚卖完了所有东西  抱歉
Hey, officer, we just sold out of everything. I'm sorry.
我也是  我错过了什么
Me, too. So, what did I miss?
天啊  有龙虾肉馅饼
Oh, my god. Lobster pot pies,
韩式肋排筒  培根奶酪通心粉棒
Korean short rib waffle cones, bacon mac and cheese pops,
你能想到的我们都有
You name it, we had it.
那你们有许可证吗
Did you happen to have a permit?
什么的许可
For what now?
营业许可  健康许可
Business permit, health permit,
-商业车辆驾照  -等等
- Commercial driver's license-- - Hold on!
稍等
One second.
-杰克  -没有
- Jake? - No.
-没有...  -都没有
- No to... - All of those.
好吧  警官  我们可能有点...
Okay, um... officer, we may have a little--
女士  请把车钥匙给我
Ma'am, hand over the keys.
我们要拖走你们的车
We're towing your truck.
什么  不  杰克  想想办法啊
What? No! Jake, do something.
或许我们该找乔什
Um... maybe we should call Josh.
给  警官  我们关门了
Here you go, officer. Guess we're shut down.
-我们该打给...  -关门了
- We should call-- - We're shut down!
艾略特  今天糟糕透了
Elliot , this is the worst day ever.
如果我给你张一千块的支票
If I give you a check for a thousand dollars,
你能闭嘴吗
can I not hear why?
我也想
Yeah, I wish.
埃兰坚持要补偿你为婚礼付出的劳动
Alan is insisting we pay you for the work you did on the wedding.
天啊  这太棒了
Oh, my god. This is amazing.
我可以赎回车子  给杰克一个惊喜
I can surprise Jake with the truck!
-我爱你  我爱你  -好恶心  好恶心
- I love you, I love you... - I have this, I hate this...
所以我才相信史提夫·汪达不是盲人
And that's why I'm convinced that Stevie Wonder can see!
总之  夏皮罗拉比
Anyway, Rabbi Shapiro...
您要能祝福我们就太好了
to get your blessing would be a real mitzvah.
再跟我说说你们的关系吧
So, tell me more about your relationship.
我觉得我们是注定要在一起的
I think that we're fated to be together.
他是我的伍迪·艾伦  我是他的宋宜
He's my Woody Allen, and I'm his Soon Yi.
我们喜欢笑  喜欢开玩笑
We laugh, we kid...
喜欢闭嘴
we stop.
你们平时会吵架吗
So, what are the areas of conflict in your relationship?
-吵架  -我们吗
- Conflict?  - Us?
怎么会
As if.
我们唯一争吵的  就是谁更爱谁
The only thing we argue about is who loves the other more.
我们甚至会说完对方的...
We even finish each other's...
说完对方的...
We finish each other's...
就像您看见的  拉比  我们很幸福
So as you can see, Rabbi, we are a delight.
您会祝福我们吗
Do we have your blessing?
我觉得我们还得见一次面
I think that we are going to have to meet again,
然后再说吧
And then we'll see.
那就是有可能咯
So it's a maybe?
是再说吧
It's a we'll see.
句子
Sentences!
我们会说完对方的句子
We finish each other's sentences!
乔什  你看到加比没
Hey, Josh, have you seen Gabi?
怎么  你俩吵架了吗
Why? Did you guys have a fight?
事情很糟糕对不对  不是吧
Did something go horribly wrong? I hope not.
实际上  是的
Actually, something did.
加比不想让我说
Gabi didn't want me to say anything,
但我不想瞒着你
But I hate to keep secrets.
昨晚餐车被扣了
The truck got impounded last night,
因为我不知道还要申请许可
'cause I didn't know we had to get permits.
所以你们没有很成功吗
So, it wasn't a huge success?
对  是场惨败
No, dude. It was a fiasco.
果然
It was!
是吗  真替你惋惜
It was... and I feel horrible.
你看起来不像  怎么回事
You don't look like you do. What's the deal?
你还在生我花钱买餐车的气吗
Are you still mad 'cause I spent the money on the truck?
不  和餐车无关
No. It's not about the truck.
-我不在乎餐车  -那就是...
- I don't care about the truck. - So then it's...
加比吗  不是加比
Gabi? No. It's not about Gabi.
天啊
Oh, my god.
不敢相信我从没想到过
I can't believe I never thought about this.
-你是喜欢她吗  -什么
- Are you into her? - What?
我吗
Me?
你怎么会想到这上面
Where would you come up with something like that?
你刚才平白无故地说了她名字
Well, you just blurted out her name for no reason,
怪不得你会是这反应
which would explain the way you've been acting.
什么
What?
太荒唐了  什么
That is ridic-- what?
这下就说得通了
This is totally making sense.
所以你想把我送去老远的
That's why you wanted to send me across the country
烹饪学校  你想赶走我
to cooking school-- you wanted to get rid of me
因为你喜欢她
because you like her.
杰克  这...
Jake, that's...
好吧  你没胆承认是吗  我有
Fine. You don't have the balls to admit it? I do.
我喜欢她
I like her.
乔什  我真的喜欢她
Josh, I really like her.
好吧
Fine.
你想要胆子是吗
You want balls?
我也喜欢她
I like her, too.
杰克  猜猜谁拿到...城市之钥了
Jake! Guess who got the keys to the f-- city?
因为市长  艾德·李
Because the mayor, Ed Lee,
喜欢我们的餐车
likes our food truck!
我走了
I-- I'm out of here.
杰克  怎么回事
Jake, what's going on?
对不起  加比  我需要些空间
I'm sorry, Gabi. I just need some space.
乔什  发生了什么
Josh, what's going on?
杰克不跟我说话
Okay, Jake's not talking to me.
乔什也不跟你说话
Well, Josh isn't talking to you, either.
如果加比诚心地问呢
Well, what if Gabi asked nicely?
是我和我弟弟的一点小矛盾
It's just a little issue between me and my brother
现在激化了
that happened to flare up.
好吧  我不是自恋哈
Okay, I don't mean this in an egotistical way at all,
但有可能是因为我吗
but could it possibly be about Gabi?
可能吧
Maybe.
他说我喜欢你
Look, he accused me of being into you.
那你跟他说了你不喜欢吗
Well, did you tell him that you're not?
我跟他说...
I told him...
我说...
加比  你怎么能在我说
Gabi, how can you date my brother
我爱你三个月以后  就跟我弟弟约会
when three months ago I told you I loved you?
什么  乔什
What, Josh?
我们不是聊过了吗
We talked about this, okay?
你说你想我们当朋友
You said you wanted to be friends.
是  加比
Yes, Gabi.
可朋友不会约前任的...
And friends don't go dating their ex...
差点是什么的弟弟
almost something's brother.
但朋友幸福朋友不该高兴吗
But shouldn't friends be happy when their friend is happy?
那我猜我们不是朋友
Then I guess we're not friends.
我猜是的
Well, I guess we're not.
我根本不想要这餐车
I don't even want this truck anymore.
我家钥匙还在上面
My house keys are on there.
谢谢您回来  拉比
Thanks for coming back, Rabbi.
毕竟婚礼就在明天了
After all, the wedding is tomorrow.
是吗
Is it?
虽然有上帝在天上保佑
Not for nothing, but god willing,
但天堂都比不上
when I go to heaven, it'll pale in comparison
我和艾略特在一起的每一刻
to the eternal bliss I feel every moment I spend with Elliot.
行了  我看够了
That's it. I have seen enough.
那您会祝福我们吗
So, do we get your blessing?
不会
I don't think so.
什么
What?
天啊
Oh, god.
我妈不会同意我们结婚的
My mother will never let us get married now.
同意吗
Let us?
少当妈宝了
Cut the damn umbilical cord already!
你都九十岁了
You're 90.
这跟我妈妈无关  是传统
It's not about my mother. It's about tradition.
你要跟我看过《屋顶上的小提琴手》就会知道
You'd know that if you'd ever watch Fiddler with me.
你一天到晚引用那台词  我还需要看吗
Who needs to watch it when you're always quoting it?
够了
That is enough.
夏皮罗拉比  抱歉让您看到这样
Rabbi Shapiro, I'm so sorry you had to see this.
不用道歉
No, you shouldn't be.
我终于看到你们像对情侣了
Finally, I get to see you as a couple!
情侣会斗嘴  会吵架
Couples fight. Couples have arguments.
这是很健康正常的
That's healthy and normal.
那我们就是您见过最健康正常的情侣了
Well, then we're the most healthy, normal couple you'll ever meet.
你这话什么意思
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
好了
There you go.
我祝福你们
You have my blessing.
-真的吗  -对
- We do? - Yes.
好棒
Yay!
我们去打电话给我妈
Oh! Let's go call my mother.
-然后祈祷她不会接  -你好大胆子
- And pray we get voicemail. - How dare you!
你好  夏皮罗拉比
Hey, Rabbi Shapiro.
乔舒亚  谢谢你请我来你家
Joshua, thank you so much for inviting me into your lovely home.
我祝福了那对新人
I gave the happy couple my blessing.
-我的任务完成了  -真棒
- My work here is done. - That's nice.
您想喝一杯酒吗
Hey, do you want a splash of this?
不了  谢谢
Oh, no, thank you.
我只在犹太新年
I only drink on high holidays
和主持割礼前喝酒
and just before a circumcision.
你有心事吗
Is there something on your mind?
很多心事
A lot, actually.
你肯定能想通的
Well, I'm sure you'll work it out.
我真的需要人聊聊
I can really use someone to talk to.
好  倒酒吧
All right. Start pouring.
我弟弟来了城里
My younger brother's in town,
通常  我们相处得很好
and normally, we get along great.
你能长话短说吗
Can you make this quick?
我在犹太缘上约了个愿意皈依的亚洲人
I have a J-Date with an Asian who's willing to convert.
我做了不好的事  因为我嫉妒
I did something bad because I was jealous
他和我曾经喜欢过的某人
about this new relationship that he's getting into
开始了新恋情
with somebody I used to have feelings for.
曾经喜欢还是依然喜欢
Used to or still do?
我不知道
I don't know.
可能都有吧
Both maybe?
乔舒亚  你这样很危险
Joshua, you are swimming in dangerous waters.
你听过该隐和亚伯的故事吗
Have you ever heard the story of Cain and Abel?
听过一点
Kinda.
故事的结局可不好
Spoiler alert, it does not end well.
关键在于  你是兄长
The point is, you're the older brother.
你要树立榜样
You have to set an example.
好好对他  别让你们的兄弟关系
Do right by him, lest the relationship end
以愤怒和流血结束
in anger and bloodshed.
-这也是《圣经》里说的吗  -不
- Is that also in The Bible? - No.
是《教父》第二部
Godfather: Part II.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
有请这对新人
for the first time as husband and husband...
帕克洛文斯汀夫夫
Mr. and Mr. Park-Lowenstein!
你还没有杰克的消息吗
I take it you haven't heard anything from Jake.
没有
No.
他不回我电话  我不知道他在哪
He wouldn't answer my calls. I don't know where he is.
或许乔什知道
Maybe Josh knows.
我不知道  我也没跟他说话
I wouldn't know. I'm not talking to him, either.
看  大家都在跳舞
Aw, look. Everybody's dancing.
恭喜他们了
Well, yipee skippy for them.
尤兰达
Yolanda...
能赏脸共舞吗
may I have this dance?
好啊
Oh, all right.
但你不许上我二垒
But you're not getting past second base.
我最后说一次  我有请柬
For the last time, I was invited!
杰克
Jake!
抱歉我没回你电话
I am sorry I didn't return your calls.
我有很多事情要消化
I've been very confused about everything.
我也是
So have I.
边跳舞边说吧
Dance and talk?
走
Let's do it.
乔舒亚  有时候我们得沉着
Joshua, sometimes we have to be steady
放弃最想要得事情  甚至梦想
and give up the things we want most, even our dreams.
-又是《圣经》吗  -《蜘蛛侠》
- Bible? - Spiderman.
知道吗  加比  我不想成为离间
You know Gabi, I don't want to be the guy
你和乔什的男人
to come between you and Josh.
我也不想成为离间你和乔什的姑娘
Well, I don't want to be the girl that comes between you and Josh.
那我们怎么办
So what do we do?
抱歉  我想祝酒
Excuse me, I'd like to propose a toast.
艾略特是我多年的好朋友
Elliot's been my best friend for many years,
我从没见过他比今天还要高兴
and I've never seen him happier than he is today.
这不仅是因为我包下了婚礼费用
And that's not just 'cause I'm paying for the wedding.
还有蜜月
And the honeymoon!
这我们可没讨论过
We never discussed that part.
你们找到了深爱的伴侣
You guys have found something amazing.
更棒的是  这才是开始
And best part about this is that it's just the beginning.
开始充满着奇妙
And there's magic in beginnings.
它们满是惊喜
They're full of surprises,
你永远不知道会发生什么
and you never know what's gonna happen.
所以  请举起酒杯
So, raise your glasses.
各位  敬一辈子的开始
Guys, here's to a lifetime of beginnings.
说到开始和惊喜
So, about beginnings and surprises...
我也有个要送给我弟弟
I have one for my brother...
和我的朋友
and my friend.
加比与杰克的餐车
天啊  那是我们的餐车吗
Oh, my god. Is that our truck?
对  换上了全新的顶级厨具
Yeah. It's got top of the line new appliances,
新发动机  空调  都换了
a new engine, an A.C. Unit-- the works.
看起来好棒
It looks amazing.
还有你的名字在上面
And it's got your name on it.
如果连艾德·希兰都发推
I figured if Ed Sheeran is tweeting
说你们的餐车好吃了
about how awesome your truck is,
你们就该利用这点  把它开去科切拉
you should capitalize on that and drive it down to Coachella.
科切拉吗  那可是加州最盛大的音乐节
Coachella? That's like, the biggest music festival in California.
我们不可能拿到许可的
There is no way we can get a permit for that.
是啊
Oh, right.
除非我已经帮你们拿到了
That is unless I already got you one.
没错
Yeah!
如果你们现在出发  还能在开幕之前赶到
And if you leave now, you guys can get there before it starts.
加比  我放你两周的假
Gabi, you have two weeks off.
去追寻你的梦想吧
Go follow your dream.
我不敢相信你会这样
I-- I can't believe you did this.
你确定吗
Are you sure about this?
确定
I'm sure.
我不知道该怎么谢你了
I don't know how to thank you.
你知道的
Yeah, you do.
好好照顾她
You take good care of her.
-乔什  我...  -加比
- Josh, I-- - Gabi...
我只希望你幸福
All I ever wanted was for you to be happy.
好了  各位  该扔捧花了
Okay everyone! It's time to toss the bouquet!
排好队  你们这群单身狗
Line up, you single losers!
我们的位置超好
Ooh, we got the best spot.
对吧  不可能抢不到的
Right? There's no way we don't catch this!
我接到了
Hey, I got it!
我没事  我没事
I'm okay! I'm okay!
-你好  -鲁本
- Hi. - Ruben?
你不穿三明治装了看起来真帅
You look so handsome without your sandwich suit.
你是闯进这婚礼  想浪漫地和我复合吗
Did you crash this wedding as big romantic gesture to get me back?
我是婚礼服务生
I'm a waiter.
也是个笨蛋
And an idiot.
居然会和你分手
I can't believe I broke up with you.
你是婚礼上最美的姑娘
You're the prettiest girl here.
继续
Go on...
-我能请你喝一杯吗  -这里酒水免费
- Can I buy you a drink? - Well, it's an open bar.
所以  多请我喝几杯吧
So you know, you can buy me several.
我猜这意思是你单身咯
So, I guess that means you're single.
没错
I am.
谢谢你  上帝
Thank you, jesus!
-无意冒犯  -没事
- No offense. - No.
你不会碰巧有犹太血统吧
You don't by any chance have any Jewish in you?
没有
I do not...
不过  今晚还长着呢
but, the evening is young.